





Summary

Jump to Section

Trusted and proven technology leader with 16+ years of rich experience in IT with proven capabilities in Delivery Management, Project Management, Quality Management and Agile Implementation. Expertise in Ecommerce, Retail, Health care and Payroll domains and worked onsite-offshore model with various BU's across different

# **Work Experience**

countries USA, UK, and Australia.

Neurocrafts Pvt. Ltd as Director of Customer Success Sep 2020 to Till Date

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Key Skills Product Development (Al, ML, Deep learning and Neural networks) Customer Success Marketing Pre-Sales and Sales

Nisum Technologies PVT LTD, as Sr. Delivery Manager Nov 2017 to Aug 2020

Key Skills End-End Delivery Framework Development Product Development Code Coverage Project Management Building the Practices Agile - BDD Selenium Cucumber Kibana Elastic Search

ADP PVT LTD, as Manager Feb 2008 to Oct 2017

Key Skills QE Automation Framework Development Product Development Code Coverage Complete QE Activities Gap Analysis Product Quality & Delivery VMManagement Code Reviews Defect Tracking Production Support Product SME

^ Back to Top

### Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Electrical and Electronics Engineering) from NBKR Institute of Science and Technology, Vidyanagar in 1999

^ Back to Top

# 1

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

#### .. 🔾.....

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience	
JAVA		
SELENIUM		
cucumber		
SOAP		
Rest Assure		
Kibana		
Elastic Search		
JMETER		
Python		

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

^ Back to Top

## **Affirmative Action**

# **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.